Kerem ZOR

CSS & UI Developer — from Istanbul, Turkey

Hello, I'm Kerem. I am 22 years old. I live in Istanbul. I am a freelance web interface developer. At the same time, I am a 4th year student at Istanbul Kültür University, Department of Visual Communication Design. I am currently working on a freelance basis. I can develop products that provide you pixel-perfect, high-performance experiences.

keremzorr@gmail.com

keremzor.github.io

github.com/keremzor

linkedin.com/keremzor

Education

Visual Communation Design

Istanbul Kultur University

2017 — 2021, Istanbul — Turkey

Web Design

Mehmet Kemal Coskunoz Industrial Vocational High School

2013 — 2017, Bursa — Turkey

Experience

CSS & UI Developer (web)

Freelance

2014 — Present

I am currently an active freelancer and also work freelance in the gaps between my work experience.

CSS & UI Developer (web)

NETUCE

2018 — 2018, Istanbul, Turkey (Office)

My second remote working experience. User interfaces are coded as compatible with all platforms. Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript (jQuery, webpack, gulp.js)

Industry Knowledge

Frontend Development

Product Design

UI & UX Design

Other Skills

HTML5 & CSS3

SCSS — OOCSS — BEM Methodologies

JavaScript (jQuery) & Pure

webpack & gulp.js

Design Tools

Figma, Sketch, Zeplin, Adobe Xd, Ps

Languages

Turkish — Native Speaking

English — Working knowledge